blast4traffic.com 2013-10-05

# Blast4Traffic™ Privacy Policy

**Blast4Traffic.com** recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personal information about our customers. Personal information includes all of the personally identifying information that is provided to Blast4Traffic.com. Blast4Traffic.com is sensitive to these privacy interests and believes that protecting valuable personal/financial information is one of Blast4Traffic.com's most significant responsibilities.

The policies outlined below describe Blast4Traffic.com's policies to protect your privacy. 

**Use, Collection and Retention of Client Information  
**Blast4Traffic.com collects, retains and uses only the information about our customers that is required by law to administer Blast4Traffic.com's business and provide high-level services to our clients. We retain this information no longer than necessary to meet these objectives.

**Maintenance of Accurate Information**  
Blast4Traffic.com has established procedures so that a client's financial information is accurate, current and complete in accordance with reasonable commercial standards. Any request to correct inaccurate information is responded to within a timely manner.

**Limiting Employee Access to Information  
**All Blast4Traffic.com employees are educated about the importance of privacy and confidentiality. Only those employees having a business reason for knowing such information have access to personally identifiable information. 

**Protection of Information via Established Security Procedures  
**Blast4Traffic.com maintains rigorous security standards and procedures regarding unauthorized access to customer information. 

**Restrictions on the Disclosure of Account Information  
**Blast4Traffic.com provides information about customer accounts or other personally identifiable data to third parties only when 1) the information is provided to help complete a customer initiated transaction, 2) the customer requires it, 3) the disclosure is required by/or allowed by law, or 4) it is necessary to process transactions and provide our services. 

**Maintaining Customer Privacy in Business Relationships with Third Parties  
**If it is necessary to provide personally identifiable customer information to a third party, Blast4Traffic.com shall insist that the third party adhere to similar privacy principles that provides for keeping such information confidential. 

**Disclosure of Privacy Principles to Customers  
**Blast4Traffic.com customers have the right to know what information we keep about them and how the information is used. Customers have the right to have any inaccurate information corrected or deleted. 

Information about your computer, and or IP address is obtained strictly for security and log in purposes.

* * *
